beautyineverything.com 2019-04-18

# Beauty in Everything

## Privacy Policy

Welcome to **Beauty in Everything** ("we," "us" , "our", the "Website" or the "Service")

### Information we collect from you

We collect Non-Personal Information only. Non-Personal Information includes information that cannot be used to personally identify you, such as anonymous usage data, general demographic information we may collect, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, preferences you submit and preferences that are generated based on the data you submit and number of clicks.

To use the Website thereafter, you do not need to submit further Personal Information. However, in an effort to improve the quality of the Service, we track information provided to us by your browser or by our software application when you view or use the Website, such as the website you came from (known as the “referring URL”), the type of browser you use, the device from which you connected to the Website, the time and date of access, and other information that does not personally identify you. We track this information using cookies, or small text files which include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to a user’s browser from our servers and are stored on the user’s computer hard drive. Sending a cookie to a user's browser enables us to collect Non-Personal information about that user and keep a record of the user’s preferences when utilizing our services, both on an individual and aggregate basis. The Website may use both persistent and session cookies; persistent cookies remain on your computer after you close your session and until you delete them, while session cookies expire when you close your browser.

### How we use your information

We use Non-Personal Information to help us improve the Website and customize the user experience. This Privacy Policy does not limit in any way our use or disclosure of Non-Personal Information and we reserve the right to use and disclose such Non-Personal Information to our partners, advertisers and other third parties at our discretion.

### Children's Privacy

Beauty in Everything does not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13. The Service and its content are not directed at children under the age of 13.

### Other websites and services

We are not responsible for the practices employed by any websites or services linked to or from our Service, including the information or content contained within them. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Service to another website or service, our Privacy Policy does not apply to those third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link on our website, are subject to that third party's own rules and policies. 

### Updates to this Privacy Policy

Beauty in Everything may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it periodically. Your continued use of the Service after any modification to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such modification.
